[MUSIC]
[موسيقى]
We've now learned decision trees from data.
لقد تعلمنا الآن تسلسل القرار من البيانات.
Let's look at how we can make predictions from it.
دعونا ننظر إلى الكيفية التي يمكننا بها التنبؤ من خلال ذلك التسلسل.
So given the model that we've learned from the data, we're going to predict y hat.
بالنظر إلى النموذج الذي تعلمناه من البيانات، سنقوم بتنبؤ y hat.
As we discussed in the beginning of the module, it's a pretty simple process
وكما ناقشنا في بداية الوحدة، هي عملية بسيطة جدًا
of traversing down the tree in order to make that prediction.
تتمثل في عبور التسلسل بالترتيب لإصدار هذا التنبؤ.
Given that particular input xi, so going back to that first example where Credit
وبالنظر إلى الإدخال xi، والرجوع إلى المثال الأول حيث كان الائتمان
was poor, Income was high, and the Term was 5 years, we go down the branch of
ضعيفًا، وكان الدخل مرتفعًا، وكانت المدة 5 سنوات، ونحن نذهب إلى أسفل الفرع
the decision tree that is associated with those particular inputs, and
من تسلسل القرار المرتبط بتلك المدخلات الخاصة،
we make a prediction that y hat i is Safe.
ليكون التوقع هو أن y hat i آمن.
This would be explicit,
سيكون هذا أكثر وضوحًا،
even that prediction algorithm is what's called a recursive algorithm.
حتى أن خوارزمية التوقع تسمى بخوارزمية متكررة.
I'm trying to predict, for a particular decision tree,
حيث أحاول التنبؤ، بتسلسل قرار معين،
I start with the top node and my input set.
أبدأ مع العقدة العلوية ومجموعة المدخلات.
And then I say, if the current node is a leaf, return,
ثم أقول، إذا كانت العقدة الحالية هي ورقة، ارجع،
predict whatever is on that leaf.
وتوقع ما هو موجود في تلك الورقة.
If it's not a leaf, then pick the child that agrees with the input and
إذا لم تكن ورقة، فاختر الفرع الذي يتوافق مع المدخلات
then recurse on that child.
ثم كرر الأمر مع هذا الفرع.
So return the prediction the child makes.
لتحصل على التنبؤ الذي أصدره الفرع.
And then that process is going to unroll that path down the tree in order
سوف تسحب تلك العملية هذا المسار لأسفل التسلسل
to make the prediction.
لعمل التنبؤات.
[MUSIC]
[موسيقى]